No guards?
It seems too quiet.
Let's hurry.
Your Majesty! Your Highness!
Are you all right, Your Highness?!
Your Majesty!
R-Run, Mia...
He... Julius...
Called upon dark power...
Hello, Philia, my destined one...
We meet again.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Episode 11
"Archdemon Asmodeus"
Philia, I see you still have that
beautiful silver hair.
And, of course, the most
beautiful soul of all.
You truly should belong to me.
Asmodeus... For what reason are
you impersonating Prince Julius?
No particular reason.
But for our love to thrive, I thought
you would find it more convenient
if I were a human rather than a demon.
Miss Philia, what's happened to Prince Julius?
He's been possessed by Archdemon Asmodeus.
I'm sure that that fool of a prince,
out of all possible options,
invoked forbidden power
to get out of the fire.
You've got an exorcist as well?
Hey, been a while!
Old Man Asmodeus.
You're looking pretty handsome today.
Mammon, eh?
You've been reduced to serving
as an exorcist's familiar.
You're a disgrace to our kind.
I'm sorry, Philia.
It must be hard to hear my romantic
overtures with all this noise.
Therefore, I intend...
to destroy everyone else here.
What are these things?
Asmodeus's shadows.
Low-ranking demons.
Silver Judgment.
They just keep coming.
Mammon!
You got it, Big Sis!
Exorcism technique: Demon-Devouring Crow!
Oh, Mammon!
You're so much cuter in that form!
You think I'm a pet or something?!
We'd better get in there, too!
It's time to debut the anti-demon weapons
that Saint Philia developed for us.
Let's begin!
Ninja technique: Art of Fire Escape!
When it comes to cleaning up...
I'm very thorough!
Indeed.
In all respects, we must be flawless.
I'm Saint Philia's butler, after all.
Incredible!
This is quite a halberd you made, Miss Philia!
A-Amazing...
Silver Judgment!
Aunt Hilde!
Teacher...
Philia. Mia.
I'm sure we have a lot of catching up to do.
But let us focus on the enemy at hand for now.
Yes, ma'am!
Honestly. I just wanted
to secure a quiet place to talk.
How obnoxious.
Incoming!
Philia! Mia!
Holy Shield!
Thanks, Miss Philia!
I'm just glad you're safe.
Such power...
I'd expect no less of the archdemon that
nearly destroyed the world four centuries ago.
But if he's using a human host,
his revival isn't complete.
Meaning this will be our
only chance to defeat him.
You're responsible for all of this.
We'll vanquish you.
You have me in a quandary.
I was hoping to preserve your beauty
in taking you back with me...
I know. Why don't we try this?
Holy Shield!
Aunt Hilde!
Teacher!
Former saint of Girtonia,
Hildegarde Adenauer...
Not the hostage I was hoping for.
Wow, Philia!
It looks like this woman's
put you through quite a lot.
I can look through the memories
of any human I touch.
Hildegarde.
You're keeping a secret
from Philia, aren't you?
Don't you dare!
She doesn't need to hear that!
Philia, if you want to save your mother,
you'll come with me.
My... mother?
The people you thought were your
parents stole you from her,
all to preserve their family line.
And it seems your little sister knew.
Philia!
Abandon me!
I abandoned you!
A mother who'd abandon her daughter
has no right to call herself one!
Teacher...
Listen to me, Philia.
What matters most to a saint is her kingdom.
You must always put your people first.
Yes, Teacher.
All this time, I've followed
her teachings as a saint.
But...
What is it you want to do?
What's right or wrong
isn't important right now.
Search deep inside you
and tell me what you really want!
I will not abandon you, Teacher!
Philia...
Sister...
Come back, Philia!
If Asmodeus gets his hands on you...
Let's do it, Mammon.
Sheesh, you really put me through my paces.
There you are.
Get down, Philia!
Blast him! Dark Matter!
You think you're strong enough for me?
Actually...
That wasn't meant to beat you, old man.
Are you all right, Teacher?!
Yes.
Begone,
fragile human!
Erza!
Sister!
Miss Philia!
Why...
It seems I've damaged your body.
No matter. I have a far better
vessel prepared for you.
One more befitting Fianna's soul.
Sister!
Now then, farewell.
This is the worst possible outcome.
If only I'd been stronger...
This can't be... My sister is...
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
As an exorcist, do you
have the ability to locate her?
Yes.
R-Really?
Tell us! Where is she?
If you refuse to reveal her whereabouts...
Himari, it's not nice to threaten people.
However...
As great as my concern for my mistress is,
it may be difficult to maintain
my gentlemanly composure.
Asmodeus's true form resides in Limbo,
between here and the Demon Realm.
He plans to use Philia's soul
to resurrect the legendary Archsaint Fianna.
Hold out just a bit longer, Philia.
Once your soul is released,
you'll be freed from such bodily pain.
I can't hold on any longer...
Are you trembling?
You poor thing...
What in the world?!
Saint Heal!
Observing Mammon gave me the chance
to study the bodies of demons.
In addition to blood, you have
a constant flow of magic power
circulating throughout you.
So when I inject magic of my own,
the two clash, temporarily
interrupting that flow.
Philia...
Why... Why are you doing this?
Don't... Don't you see how much I love you?!
That's why I came to get you!
Silver Judgment!
Miss Erza, you know a way
to get to Limbo, don't you?
What if I do?
Demonic affairs fall under the
jurisdiction of exorcists like me.
I can't have royals, or even saints,
getting involved.
As far as coming and going with
my teleportation magic is concerned,
carrying you and Philia,
I'd only be able to take one more person.
Mammon!
Look, you owe Philia your life, right?
You can see why someone'd
want to save her, right?
Then the answer is obvious!
I'll go to save Philia!
I'm afraid that's out of the
question, Your Highness!
As Saint Philia's butler, I—
I cannot simply stay here!
I must be the one to save my sister!
It is my duty as retainer to save my lady.
Let it be me!
What's a maid if she's not
serving her mistress?!
Please take me with you!
Sh-Sheesh, you guys!
Not that I mind having pretty
girls up in my face...
This is Philia.
Can you hear me?
Philia's talking out of my bracelet!
I included a function to communicate through
it via magic should such a need arise.
Sister! Are you all right?
How's your wound?
It's fine now.
I'm sorry to have worried you all.
We're just glad you're okay!
You can get back to us, right?
Miss Philia?
Prince Osvalt...
This might be the last time we speak.
Wh-What?
What does that mean?!
Before Asmodeus regains his full power...
I must destroy him here.
Don't, Sister!
Not even you can defeat that awful monster!
I will find a way, Mia.
It's not completely out of the question.
Moreover...
It is my wish to return to Parnacorta.
Sister...
Philia.
Teacher.
I have so many questions for you.
But I'm genuinely glad to know the truth.
I see.
You've grown up very strong.
The things you taught me were priceless.
I will not let them be for nothing.
Miss Philia!
Prince Osvalt...
I swear it... I swear I'm going to save you!
Do you remember my offer to you that day?
Once this is all over...
Could we go out together again?
For a meal, this time.
I'm going to keep my word! So...
Miss Erza!
Please, take me to Miss Philia!
Didn't I tell you before?
I cannot grant that request, even to you.
I understand your reasoning!
But the life of the person who
matters most to me is on the line!
So I can't let that talk me down!
Is Philia so important to you?
That you'd give your life for hers?
You're damn right!
No matter what happens,
I'm going to save her!
Erza.
Please, let him go.
I'd like to do it myself, but...
Please take Prince Osvalt in my place.
Miss Mia...
I'm throwing in my support, too!
Prince Osvalt, go save Saint Philia.
I defer to you, Highness.
If you insist.
There's no guarantee you'll
make it back, though.
We're off, then.
Prince Osvalt.
Please, look after my daughter.
Ms. Hildegarde...
Leave it to me.
I swear I'll bring Miss Philia back!
So she can keep smiling with all of us!
I see...
That's the smile that melted
the ice over my sister's heart.
Prince Osvalt!
We'll handle these. Go!
Right!
I don't need him anymore.
I won't get any further
possessing that frail shell.
So this is your true form?
Yes.
It's been four centuries since
I last faced you like this.
Philia...
No, soul of Fianna.
I'm so glad you're here.
Do you know how I've waited these
four hundred years to meet you again?
Now, let us spend eternity together!
I have prepared the perfect body for you!
Two hundred years of craftsmanship
from the finest dollmakers...
It took so much work to perfectly
recreate Fianna's body.
Now, let's begin the ritual.
First, I'll move your soul to its new vessel,
then I'll draw out Fianna's
memories embedded within.
I do dislike the use of force.
I was hoping you'd offer
up your soul willingly.
What are you—
Now, will you save this man or not?
I'm very curious.
Personally, I'd love to see you
abandon your once former fiancé.
Abandon him?
Yes.
His unbridled jealousy led him
to heap abuse upon you for ages.
And then he sold you off like garbage!
I won't tolerate anyone
who'd treat you that way!
So if you ask me to kill him,
I will do so gladly.
I surrender.
Release Prince Julius.
You'd decide without hesitation, hmm?
Such unwavering strength of spirit...
That really is what I expect from you.
I won't resist.
But first, release the prince.
No, I need to bind you first.
I can't have you channeling
magic into me again.
Fianna! At last, I'll see you again!
I won't let you have Miss Philia!
I had faith, Prince Osvalt.
I knew that you would come.
And if you, so eternally
forthright, are truly here...
then I have reason to hope.
Next time, episode 12:
"The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé, Now in Another Kingdom."
Next Time
Episode 12
"The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside by My Fiancé, Now in Another Kingdom"